<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting started on cu.css</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting started on cu.css</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 16:42:27 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 16:42:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/installation/</guid>
      <description>There are currently two different ways to install cu.css in your project, depending on whether you prefer to work with CSS or SASS.&#xA;Installing CSS Follow these steps if you plan to work with CSS:&#xA;Download the full project from Github. Copy main.css or main.min.css from the public/css folder into your project. Copy the fonts directory into your project. The final step is to link to your stylesheet file inside the &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; of your pages:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working with CSS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/working-with-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 16:42:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/working-with-css/</guid>
      <description>If you plan to customise or build upon cu.css, then you will find it much easier to work with the unminified css found in public/css/main.css. If you wish to use cu.css without modification, then working with the minified CSS found in public/css/main.min.css will ensure the smallest file size.&#xA;The stylesheets in public/css contain configurations for custom fonts, customising the theme of cu.css, and managing fluid type and space scales. Most of these configurations consist of CSS custom properties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working with SASS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/working-with-sass/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 16:42:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/working-with-sass/</guid>
      <description>You can find the Sass files for cu.css inside the assets/scss directory. You may find working with Sass gives you a little more flexibility when customising.&#xA;Understanding the directory structure Inside assets/scss you will find 5 directories and a bunch of files.&#xA;The abstracts directory contains the project configurations outlined above: @font-face declarations for including custom fonts in the project. CSS custom properties for theming. CSS custom properties for Utopia fluid type and space scales.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
